<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advocacy Website</title>
    <link>https://manguilar22.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Advocacy Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 15:13:31 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://manguilar22.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Centers</title>
      <link>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/data-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/data-center/</guid>
      <description>What are data centers ? In the advent of cloud computing, companies are preparing to clear land to make room for warehouses. These warehouses are made to house the worlds computing power. Companies rely on these warehouses and their performance to ensure the best services provided to their customers. These warehouses are running software that is responsible for streaming services and other business offerings. However, these warehouse use a lot of energy and this essay plans on showing how different forms of media try to raise awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographic</title>
      <link>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/infographic/</guid>
      <description>Top Super Powers in computing. This section will highilght the most powerful nations in computing. All these visualizations were done in the wolfram language. The visualizations hope to achieve a visual comprehension to the issue.  This demonstrates the heat dissipation created by a CPU. A CPU is responsible for carrying out all computations and therefore creates heat. We can see in this picture the heat produced covers almost the entire board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem</title>
      <link>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/problem/</guid>
      <description>Genre Analysis Media: Scientific Article Asesses the energy consumption of data centers, because it will increase in the future.
Media: Video YouTube
Introduction The topic of focus is cloud computing, hoping to explore more about cloud computing. Not the benefits people get from cloud computing, but the consequences. The consequences that come from building monumental warehouses that only purpose is to store computers. These computers are working in unison and require a lot of electricity for a warehouse to run the entire year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/initial-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manguilar22.github.io/docs/initial-questions/</guid>
      <description>Ecological improvements in the field of computing Abstract As a society we have becomed accustomed to instant entertainment. We personally get satisfaction from the many services that are sold online. Subscription based packages that include movies, music, or vendor preference. These services are multi-billion dollar industry with great investment in creating large warehouses to store computers. These warehouse, known as data- centers are responsible for providing all their content to paying customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Page One</title>
      <link>https://manguilar22.github.io/posts/page-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 15:13:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manguilar22.github.io/posts/page-one/</guid>
      <description>Post - one This is still post one This is a post This another post </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>